<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
    <title>Expats.top</title>
    <link href="https://expats.top/feed.xml" rel="self" />
    <link href="https://expats.top" />
    <updated>2024-02-01T13:14:06+01:00</updated>
    <author>
        <name>sxiii</name>
    </author>
    <id>https://expats.top</id>

    <entry>
        <title>Gallery</title>
        <author>
            <name>sxiii</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://expats.top/gallery-2/"/>
        <id>https://expats.top/gallery-2/</id>

        <updated>2024-02-01T13:10:59+01:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    Thursday Board Games - 2024 Thursday Board Games - 2023 Thursday Board Games - 2022 Thursday Board Games - 2021
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p><strong>Thursday Board Games - 2024</strong></p>
<p><strong>Thursday Board Games - 2023</strong></p>
<p><strong>Thursday Board Games - 2022</strong></p>
<p><strong>Thursday Board Games - 2021</strong></p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Thursday Board Games</title>
        <author>
            <name>sxiii</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://expats.top/tbg/"/>
        <id>https://expats.top/tbg/</id>

        <updated>2024-02-01T13:14:06+01:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    Location: House of Nerds (Vulkan, 18) Date: every Thursday&nbsp; Start Time: 17:30 Roll into the excitement every Thursday at our&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                
  <p>
    <b>Location: </b>House of Nerds (Vulkan, 18)<br><b>Date: </b>every Thursday&nbsp;<br><b>Start Time: </b>17:30<br>
  </p>

  <p>
    Roll into the excitement every Thursday at our Weekly Board Game Night! Join fellow enthusiasts for a recurring evening of strategic gameplay, friendly competition, and a welcoming community of gamers. Whether you're a seasoned player or a novice, our Thursday nights are dedicated to laughter, camaraderie, and discovering new board game favorites. Bring your competitive spirit and join us as we make each Thursday memorable with a fresh array of tabletop adventures.&nbsp;Feel free to bring your own board games, adding a personal touch to our game night. And don't worry if you're running a bit late – we'll have a seat waiting for you.<br><br>NB: This is a free event and everyone's welcomed.<br><br>Now you can donate to our event (if you want), so we could buy more games for everyone's enjoyment faster! :)<br><br>~ ~ ~ Food &amp; Drinks ~ ~ ~<br>Drinks will be available on site for purchase. Food is available in Mathallen. You are allowed to bring your food to HoN facility.<br><br>~ ~ ~ Being late and getting help ~ ~ ~<br>If you can't come at the beginning of the event, that's totally OK. You can basically come any time you like (during event hours). We will try to arrange a play group for you at all times. If you need help with finding a game or spot, ask me (Den).<br><br>~ ~ ~ Donations ~ ~ ~<br>If possible, please, either add message "Board games donation", or if the payment provider you're using does not support that function or you don't want to use it, please donate any amount that ends with 1337, for example, 113.37 NOK.<br><br>    Vipps 98770410 or https://qr.vipps.no/28/2/01/031/4798770410?v=1<br>    SBanken 98023234092<br>    https://revolut.me/sxiii<br>    Crypto donate coming soon!<br>
  </p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Links</title>
        <author>
            <name>sxiii</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://expats.top/links/"/>
        <id>https://expats.top/links/</id>

        <updated>2024-02-01T12:56:18+01:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    Useful links for Expats
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                
  <p>
    <em>Useful links for Expats</em>
  </p>

  <ul>
    <li>Main <a href="https://www.meetup.com/expats-in-oslo/" target="_blank">Expats meetup community</a></li><li>Used &amp; new things market; rent &amp; sell houses and apartments, boats, cars, find job and more: <a href="https://finn.no" target="_blank">finn.no</a></li><li>Rent house or apartment: <a href="https://hybel.no" target="_blank">hybel.no</a></li><li>Work in Norway:&nbsp;<a href="https://nav.no" target="_blank">nav.no</a></li><li>The Norwegian Directorate of Immigration: <a href="https://udi.no" target="_blank">udi.no</a></li><li>Service Center for Foreign Workers: <a href="https://www.sua.no/en/" target="_blank">sua.no</a></li><li>Telegram group for people who would like to move to Norway or Scandinavia (mostly Russian-speaking community): <a href="https://t.me/@waytonorway" target="_blank">@waytonorway</a><br></li>
  </ul>

  <p>
    <br>
  </p>

  <p>
    
  </p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Partners</title>
        <author>
            <name>sxiii</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://expats.top/partners/"/>
        <id>https://expats.top/partners/</id>

        <updated>2024-02-01T12:20:54+01:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    ITMeet.top - International Tech Meetups community Web3F.top - Web3, Crypto and Blockchain Events
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                
  <p>
    <a href="https://itmeet.top" target="_blank">ITMeet.top</a> - International Tech Meetups community<br><a href="https://web3f.top" target="_blank">Web3F.top</a> - Web3, Crypto and Blockchain Events
  </p>

  <p>
    
  </p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>History</title>
        <author>
            <name>sxiii</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://expats.top/history/"/>
        <id>https://expats.top/history/</id>

        <updated>2024-02-01T12:48:05+01:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    Expats in Oslo originally started as Meetup community around beginning of November 2010. First activity had been hosted as long&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                
  <p>
    <a href="https://www.meetup.com/expats-in-oslo/" target="_blank">Expats in Oslo</a> originally started as Meetup community around beginning of November 2010. First activity had been hosted as long as 14 years ago by <a href="https://www.meetup.com/expats-in-oslo/events/15382256/" target="_blank">Emma on 10 November 2010</a> which was a small social gathering and I think that shows up the nature of such a decentralised groups that live long enough and semi-self organise. The group changed focus several times and during different years a lot of people attended the events.
  </p>

  <p>
    To this day, Expats in Oslo meetup community hosted almost 1100 events! Throughout the years that has been pretty different events (over 30 types of activities) and currently there are 14 organisers. Out of them, about 4 organisers including me are active to this day on Meetup and you probably can meet them from time to time.
  </p>

  <p>
    The list of activities by the group includes regular board games (every Thursday and Friday), smaller gatherings to play a particular board game, occasional or summer hikes and photo shoots, networking, ice skating, cycling, comedy and impro nights, karaoke, sports, marathons, museums, tours, concerts, yoga, open mics, picnics, movie screenings, opera, music, night outs, outdoor activities, language caffees, startups events and pitches, dinners, sledding, medieval and normal festivals, and other things. Main and regular activities lately have been the board gaming gatherings.
  </p>

  <p>
    I've (Den, sxiii) joined the community 24 December 2018 - right about after arriving for my first job in Norway. I haven't been hosting any events until ~ after the corona in the middle of 2021. Originally inspired from the "House of Nerds" in Loren and later by Winston's famous Wednesday Board Games who's been hosting many board games, at some point I've decided to try to start my own event and that marks the start of the journey of my "Thursday Board Games" event - first happened on&nbsp;8 July 2021.
  </p>

  <p>
    Since then I've been able to host many Board Game Events - current statistic (1 Feb 2024) says it's been 135 events in the group - that stands for about 2.5 years of activity, if we only count "Thursday Board Games".
  </p>

  <p>
    Some years were more active than others, but overall I think every year had a lot of fun events and almost every year had more events then the previous one.
  </p>

  <p>
    Nowadays, Expats in Oslo Meetup community consists of almost 7,000 members and it continues to grow and to become an awesome and diversified platform or all kind of social events.
  </p>

  <p>
    I'd like to thank all organisers and participants for an awesome journey and I also hope that this story inspires you on one day to make own event!
  </p>

  <p>
    See you <a href="https://www.meetup.com/expats-in-oslo/events/" target="_blank">around</a>,
  </p>

  <p>
    <i>yours truly<br>Den Ivanov</i>
  </p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Events</title>
        <author>
            <name>sxiii</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://expats.top/events/"/>
        <id>https://expats.top/events/</id>

        <updated>2024-02-01T13:08:28+01:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    Right now we are hosting the following events from the Expats community: To mark the RSVP (Participation) and see all&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                
  <p>
    Right now we are hosting the following events from the Expats community:
  </p>

  <ul>
    <li><b>Board Games Thursdays</b>&nbsp;event is hosted at awesome House of Nerds facility (Vulkan, 18) across the street from Mathallen and not very far from iconic Oslo Grunerløkka area. It's happening Thursday evening, @ 17:30, every week. The games are hosted in English and you don't need to know any of the board games to come and play with us (we're happy to teach you!). You can also bring your own favourite board games if you know any! Read more about history of the event.</li><li><b>Boardgame Night and Hangout </b>at Toyen Library happens on Friday evenings (18:00 and onwards).</li>
  </ul>

  <p>
    To mark the RSVP (Participation) and see all of the available events, visit the link: <a href="https://www.meetup.com/expats-in-oslo/events/" target="_blank">https://www.meetup.com/expats-in-oslo/events/</a>
  </p>

  <p>
    <b>Our partners</b> are also hosting awesome events, please check them out:
  </p>

  <ul>
    <li><a href="https://itmeet.top" target="_blank">ITMeet.top</a> - International Tech Meetups community (already started)</li><li><a href="https://web3f.top" target="_blank">Web3F.top</a> - Web3, Crypto and Blockchain Events (upcoming in March)</li>
  </ul>

  <p>
    We are open for collaboration to host more different awesome events all across Oslo as well as online and globally, too.
  </p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Expats Community</title>
        <author>
            <name>sxiii</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://expats.top/expats-community/"/>
        <id>https://expats.top/expats-community/</id>

        <updated>2024-02-01T12:24:09+01:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    Welcome to our humble Expats community. With headquarters in Oslo - one of the world's best IT hub hosting a&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>Welcome to our humble Expats community.</p>
<p>With headquarters in Oslo - one of the world's best IT hub hosting a large set of diversified startups, we provide a myriad of different events in the city as well as provide online experience for all of you!</p>
<p>This website is a work-in-progress during February 2024, but please join along in our journey!</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
</feed>
